通常大家就叫我崔希～
Usually ponies just call me Trixie~
但「神通小姐」聽起來也不錯。
But "Miss Powerful" has a nice ring to it.
不要放我走
Please don't make me go
請你永遠都不要放我離去
please don't ever make me go away from you
不知我是誰
Don't know who I am
我真的不知我是誰，或能做什麼
I don't really know who I am, or can be
而每個小馬，都跟我說
And everypony tries to tell me
就停下來，正常一次好
to settle down and conform for once
我只跟他們說，他們沒過
But I just tell them they've never had
其物的夢想
dreams of something else
心如成駒，站直直
As strong as horses we stand tall
不論我們為何
no matter who we are
如此幼稚的情感
A sentiment so childlike
但幼駒也看得遠
but a filly can see as far
心如成駒，如成駒
As strong as horses, strong as horses
跟天空一樣的清澈
as clear as the open skies
我不想長大
I don't wanna grow
我不想要長大
I don't ever wanna grow up
我努力好久
I've tried so hard
沒有魔術能
There's no magic trick
能治好我的傷痛
to fix the pain I have
而我周遭的一切
And everything around me
感覺都好虛偽
feels as fake as nothing at all
鏡子照不出我真正的自己
Mirrors can't show me who I'm supposed to be
而你還是聽不懂
and you still can't take that hint
你只叫我堅強
You just tell me stay strong
需要時跟你發洩
and talk if I need to
我們心如成駒
We're strong as horses
你什麼都不用怕
you've got nothing to fear
我們心如成駒
We're strong as horses
閉嘴，我不需要聽
don't talk, I don't need to hear
心如成駒，站直直
As strong as horses we stand tall
不論我們為何
no matter who we are
如此幼稚的情感
A sentiment so childlike
但幼駒也看得遠
but a filly can see as far
心如成駒，如成駒
As strong as horses, strong as horses
跟天空一樣的清澈
as clear as the open skies
我不想長大
I don't wanna grow
我不想要長大
I don't ever wanna grow up
我努力好久
I've tried so hard
心如成駒，如成駒
As strong as horses, strong as horses
跟天空一樣的清澈
as clear as the open skies
心如成駒，如成駒
As strong as horses, strong as horses
跟天空一樣的清澈
as clear as the open skies
我不想長大
I don't wanna grow up
心如成駒，站直直
As strong as horses we stand tall
我們眼淚如水流
Our tears will be waterfalls